Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Whose Secret=
=سر من=
=Episode 2= (The Sister Who Returns)
=الحلقة الثانية= (الأخت العائدة)
Sister.
أخت.
I will uncover the truth of your death.
سأكشف حقيقة موتك.
The man called the Lord of Wujian
الرجل الذي يدعى سيد ووجيان
must hold the secret of your death.
يجب أن يحمل سر موتك.
(Brother.)
(أخ.)
(We have a new game.)
(لدينا لعبة جديدة.)
(I will not let him go.)
(لن أسمح له بالذهاب.)
(Yan.)
(شاب)
Sister.
أخت.
Yan.
نعم.
I miss you very much.
أفتقدك جداً جداً.
Will you come with me?
هل ستأتي معي؟
Sister.
أخت.
Lu Huayan.
لو هوايان.
Go and reminisce with your sister in the dream disc.
اذهب وتذكر أختك في قرص الحلم.
You inherited your father's lordship over Wujian.
لقد ورثت سيادة والدك على Wujian.
You do not remain in Wujian properly,
أنت لا تبقى في Wujian بشكل صحيح،
what are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Hanging up on brother like that
تعليق على الأخ بهذه الطريقة
is somewhat rude, is it not?
إنه أمر وقح إلى حد ما، أليس كذلك؟
Did you release the spirit beasts?
هل أطلقت سراح الوحوش الروحية؟
They endanger humans and Wujian's order.
إنهم يعرضون البشر ونظام ووجيان للخطر.
What wicked plan have you set in motion?
ما هي الخطة الشريرة التي وضعتها موضع التنفيذ؟
The spirit beasts escaped.
هربت الوحوش الروحية.
You govern poorly yourself,
أنت تحكم نفسك بشكل سيء،
so why blame me?
فلماذا تلوموني؟
What does that have to do with me?
ما علاقة هذا بي؟
That woman at the Paramount slashed at you.
لقد قامت تلك المرأة في باراماونت بضربك.
I taught her a lesson for you.
لقد علمتها درسًا لك.
I sealed her in the dream disc.
لقد ختمتها في قرص الحلم.
She will die soon.
إنها سوف تموت قريبا.
How amusing.
كم هو مسلي.
How will you thank me?
كيف ستشكرني؟
My good brother.
أخي الصالح.
Li Motong.
لي موتونج.
I have sealed her in the dream disc.
لقد ختمتها في قرص الحلم.
If you want to free her,
إذا كنت تريد تحريرها،
you must kill her.
يجب عليك قتلها.
But if you slaughter humans indiscriminately,
ولكن إذا ذبحت البشر دون تمييز،
you will accept Wujian's thunder punishment.
سوف تقبل عقوبة الرعد وو جيان.
This is my gift to you.
هذه هديتي لك.
A deadly trap.
فخ مميت.
I really want to see
انا حقا أريد أن أرى
how you will make your choice.
كيف ستتخذ قرارك؟
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Did you lure me here on purpose using my sister's voice?
هل أغريتني هنا عمداً باستخدام صوت أختي؟
You want to kill me?
هل تريد قتلي؟
I have no interest in human lives.
ليس لدي أي اهتمام بحياة البشر.
We are both trapped inside the dream disc.
نحن الاثنان محاصرون داخل قرص الحلم.
If you want to leave here alive,
إذا كنت تريد أن تغادر هذا المكان حيًا،
you must work with me.
يجب عليك العمل معي.
You monsters.
أيها الوحوش.
You killed my sister.
لقد قتلت أختي.
I will never cooperate with you.
لن أتعاون معك أبدًا.
If you refuse to work with me,
إذا رفضت العمل معي،
then you can only die.
حينها لن يكون بوسعك إلا أن تموت.
Even if it means death,
حتى لو كان ذلك يعني الموت،
I will never stand with you.
لن أقف معك أبدًا.
Miss Lu.
السيدة لو.
Only the living have the right to choose their fate.
إن الأحياء فقط هم من لهم الحق في اختيار مصيرهم.
The dead can only be controlled by others.
لا يمكن السيطرة على الموتى إلا من قبل الآخرين.
After so long, the dream realm
بعد كل هذا الوقت، عالم الأحلام
finally welcomes a human.
يرحب أخيرا بالإنسان.
Let's give them a grand gift.
فلنقدم لهم هدية عظيمة.
Miss Shen.
السيدة شين.
Then let's teach them
إذن فلنعلمهم
a lesson.
درس.
Brother.
أخ.
I'm truly curious.
أنا فضولي حقا.
Will you really kill this lowly human?
هل ستقتل هذا الإنسان الحقير حقا؟
Yan.
نعم.
Sister.
أخت.
I've finally found you.
لقد وجدتك أخيرا.
Where have you been?
أين كنت؟
I've been waiting every day for you to come home.
لقد كنت أنتظر عودتك إلى المنزل كل يوم.
Now I've finally found you.
والآن وجدتك أخيرا.
Then, Yan,
ثم يان،
stay by your sister's side forever,
ابقى بجانب أختك إلى الأبد،
will you?
سوف تفعل؟
All right.
حسنًا.
She isn't your sister at all.
إنها ليست أختك على الإطلاق.
You're lying.
أنت تكذب
Your sister has long been dead.
لقد ماتت أختك منذ زمن طويل.
She's just a puppet inside the dream disc.
إنها مجرد دمية داخل قرص الحلم.
Don't be fooled by this illusion.
لا تنخدع بهذا الوهم.
Lord of Wujian.
سيد ووجيان.
You have no right to interfere between us sisters,
ليس لديك الحق في التدخل بيننا يا أخوات،
am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
Sister.
أخت.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'll show you now
سأريك الآن
what lies beneath the skin
ما يكمن تحت الجلد
of the sister you keep calling out for.
من الأخت التي تستمر في مناداتها.
Then let's have some fun.
إذن فلنستمتع ببعض المرح.
Sister.
أخت.
Sister!
أخت!
(We're not done yet.)
(لم ننتهي بعد.)
Sister.
أخت.
Li Motong.
لي موتونج.
You heartless, bloodthirsty demon.
أنت شيطان بلا قلب، متعطش للدماء.
Even if she was false,
حتى لو كانت كاذبة،
she was still my only solace.
لقد كانت لا تزال عزائي الوحيد.
You shattered my dream with your own hands.
لقد حطمت حلمي بيديك.
You've seen the truth.
لقد رأيت الحقيقة.
She's nothing but a puppet in this dream disc.
إنها ليست سوى دمية في قرص الأحلام هذا.
If you wish to leave,
إذا كنت ترغب في المغادرة،
then work with me.
ثم اعمل معي.
I'll lead you out of this dream disc.
سأخرجك من قرص الحلم هذا.
You truly are beyond reason.
أنت حقا خارج نطاق العقل.
Seems I'll have to send you myself.
يبدو أنني سأضطر إلى إرسالك بنفسي.
Miss Shen.
السيدة شين.
=Whose Secret=
=سر من=
♪Her long hair with the dark night♪
♪شعرها الطويل مع الليل المظلم♪
♪Looks so pure in the lamplight♪
♪يبدو نقيًا جدًا في ضوء المصباح♪
♪Blurred flesh and tears♪
♪لحم مشوش ودموع♪
♪The evil spirit's hand pushes her into a kiss upon the rail♪
♪يد الروح الشريرة تدفعها إلى قبلة على السور♪
♪Where does the truth pretend to sleep?♪
♪أين تتظاهر الحقيقة بالنوم؟♪
♪Perfect last words confront what cannot be faced♪
♪الكلمات الأخيرة المثالية تواجه ما لا يمكن مواجهته♪
♪The scent corroded by the dawn♪
♪الرائحة المتآكلة بالفجر♪
♪Is her hollow soul tossed within a bottle♪
♪هل روحها المجوفة ملقاة داخل زجاجة♪
♪Bloodless lips bloom into bright petals♪
♪شفاه بلا دم تتفتح في بتلات مشرقة♪
♪Whispering their filthy confession♪
♪همس اعترافهم القذر♪
♪A white cat intently licks the thick sweet scent of blood♪
♪قطة بيضاء تلعق باهتمام رائحة الدم الحلوة الكثيفة♪
♪Accusing, demanding♪
♪متهم، متطلب♪
♪Who are you, who am I?♪
♪من أنت، من أنا؟♪
♪How did everything turn against itself?♪
♪كيف انقلب كل شيء ضد نفسه؟♪
♪What is striking inside the cold coffin?♪
♪ما هو الملفت للنظر داخل التابوت البارد؟♪
♪The restless bones beneath♪
♪العظام المضطربة في الأسفل♪
♪To which gravestone point her broken fingers♪
♪إلى أي شاهد قبر تشير أصابعها المكسورة♪
♪Who trembles, who grieves?♪
♪من يرتجف، من يحزن؟♪
♪Who is guiltless, who bears sin?♪
♪من هو البريء، من يتحمل الخطيئة؟♪
♪Take me to unearth redemption and fearlessness♪
♪خذني إلى اكتشاف الفداء والشجاعة♪
♪He kisses her fingertips♪
♪يقبل أطراف أصابعها♪
♪Bare joints blooming white iris♪
♪المفاصل العارية تتفتح زهور السوسن البيضاء♪
♪Nightmares and roses lie asleep♪
♪الكوابيس والورود نائمة♪
♪Nothing but a date with death♪
♪لا شيء سوى موعد مع الموت♪